It started, yeah?
Well there, the ground.
Filled in earth over the antenna today.
Nothing's connected, there's nothing, bulbs 70 watts and 23 watts, we take the battery, connect it, just start it.
We hold it, the logic catches on, it came up.
The bulb burns.
It works.
So, Roma, everything works?
Yeah, everything's excellent, the main thing is this most unpleasant block, the painstaking one, I'll unblock it later, take it apart.
Well there, that's all, this is the most unpleasant part, and everything else works.
So, everything's burning.
Super.
Yeah, Roma just didn't believe it.
Well yeah, yeah, yeah, got it.
That's all, all, well, it is what it is, yeah, I mean I say that nothing, what's it called, peak-avalanche.